import { Question } from "../interfaces/Question";

export const englishTestQuestions: Question[] = [
    {
        description: "Question 1. Select correct word:",
        question: "I ____ from Ukraine",
        options: ["Is", "Are", "Am", "Be"],
        answer: "Am",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 2. Select correct word:",
        question: "My brother is _____ programmer.",
        options: ["The", "An", "A", "For"],
        answer: "A",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 3. Select correct word:",
        question: "This is my friend. ____ name is Catherine.",
        options: ["Her", "She", "Our"],
        answer: "Her",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 4. Fill in the blank:",
        question: "_______ twenty-five desks in the class.",
        options: ["There is", "There are", "This is", "They are"],
        answer: "There are",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 5. Select correct word:",
        question: "My mom _______ like horror films.",
        options: ["Does not", "No", "Is not", "Do not"],
        answer: "Does not",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 6. Select correct word:",
        question: "I will call you later! I ___  right now.",
        options: ["`m sleeping", "Sleep", "Sleeping"],
        answer: "Sleep",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 7. Select correct word:",
        question: "She _____  at the university last Tuesday.",
        options: ["Didn’t be", "Wasn’t", "Weren’t", "Isn’t"],
        answer: "Wasn’t",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 8. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "________ a piece of cake? No, thank you.",
        options: ["Do you like", "Would you like", "Want you", "Are you like"],
        answer: "Would you like",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 9. Select correct word:",
        question: "My room is ______ than yours.",
        options: ["More big", "Most big", "Bigger", "Biggest"],
        answer: "Bigger",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 10. Select correct word:",
        question: "Vicky does not like sweets. She most likely ______ eats chocolate.",
        options: ["Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Usually"],
        answer: "Rarely",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 11. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "They ______ in the mall when it started to rain.",
        options: ["They walked", "Were walking", "Are walking", "Walk"],
        answer: "Were walking",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 12. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "_____ ever been to Australia?",
        options: ["Have you", "Did you", "Do you", "Are you"],
        answer: "Have you",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 13. Select correct word:",
        question: "We have known each other ____ high school.",
        options: ["Since", "For", "From", "While"],
        answer: "Since",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 14. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "You _____ pay for the drinks. They are free.",
        options: ["Have to", "Don’t have to", "Don’t need to", "Doesn’t have to"],
        answer: "Don’t have to",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 15. Select correct word:",
        question: "Ben was on the vacation last week and he _____ come to your party.",
        options: ["Couldn’t", "Can not", "Needn`t", "Mustn`t"],
        answer: "Couldn’t",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 16. Select correct word:",
        question: "We'll stay at home if it ______ this afternoon.",
        options: ["Raining", "Rains", "Will rain", "Rain"],
        answer: "Rains",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 17. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "John is ______ player in this team.",
        options: ["The best", "Most better", "Better than", "Best than"],
        answer: "The best",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 18. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "Paris ______  by hundreds of thousands of tourists every year.",
        options: ["Is visited", "Visiting", "Visits"],
        answer: "Is visited",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 19. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "I do not like orange juice very much. _______.",
        options: ["Neither do I", "I do not too", "I am not too"],
        answer: "Neither do I",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 20. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "I _____ bus on Mondays.",
        options: ["`m going to work with", "`m going to work by", "Go to work with", "Go to work by"],
        answer: "`m going to work by",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 21. Select correct word:",
        question: "I don't want to see her ____ the party tonight.",
        options: ["At", "On", "In"],
        answer: "At",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 22. Select correct word:",
        question: "I wasn't hungry, ___ I didn't eat.",
        options: ["So", "Because", "But", "And"],
        answer: "So",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 23. Select correct word:",
        question: "Can I stay here tonight? I have _____ to go.",
        options: ["Nowhere", "Anywhere", "Somewhere"],
        answer: "Nowhere",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 24. Select correct word:",
        question: "I wouldn't drink that milk if I ___  you.",
        options: ["Were", "`d be", "Was"],
        answer: "Were",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 25. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "I ____ work in a bank, but now I'm working as a designer.",
        options: ["Used to", "Got used to", "Was used to"],
        answer: "Used to",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 26. Select correct word:",
        question: "Don't call the police  ____ it's strictly necessary.",
        options: ["Unless", "Whether or not", "Even if"],
        answer: "Unless",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 27. Select correct word:",
        question: "I was keen _____ learning languages when I was at college.",
        options: ["On", "At", "About", "In"],
        answer: "On",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 28. Select correct word:",
        question: "Matthew is fond ____ reading and visits the library every week.",
        options: ["Of", "Doing", "About", "Going"],
        answer: "Of",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 29. Select correct word:",
        question: "I’m thinking about _____ chemistry next year because I’m finding it very boring.",
        options: ["Dropping", "Enrolling", "Failing", "Sitting"],
        answer: "Dropping",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 30. Select correct word:",
        question: "I always feel anxious before giving a _____.",
        options: ["Presentation", "Essay", "Exam", "Research"],
        answer: "Presentation",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 31. Select correct word:",
        question: "Only two people _____ for the position, so we didn’t have to do a lot of interviews.",
        options: ["Applied", "Resigned", "Quit", "Retired"],
        answer: "Applied",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 32. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "You may not like the cold weather here, but you’ll have to_____, I’m afraid.",
        options: ["Tell it off", "Put up with it", "Put it off", "Sort it off"],
        answer: "Put up with it",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 33. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "They say that the diamond _____ over €5 million.",
        options: ["Is worth", "Pays", "Can afford", "Borrows"],
        answer: "Is worth",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 34. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "It’s a good idea to _____ these files in case your computer crashes.",
        options: ["Back up", "Upgrade", "Sign up", "Browse"],
        answer: "Back up",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 35. Select correct word:",
        question: "The doctor was tired because he’d just finished a 12-hour _____.",
        options: ["Bonus", "Leave", "Shift", "Apprenticeship"],
        answer: "Shift",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 36. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "With robots replacing many jobs these days, lots of people worry about _____.",
        options: ["Being sacked", "Being made redundant", "Getting promoted", "Meeting deadlines"],
        answer: "Being made redundant",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 37. Select correct word:",
        question: "I did a short _____ at a veterinary clinic last summer.",
        options: ["Qualification", "Undergraduate", "Internship", "Project work"],
        answer: "Internship",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 38. Select correct phrase:",
        question: "The ______ on my mortgage has risen in the past year.",
        options: ["Interest rate", "Budget", "Income", "Expense"],
        answer: "Interest rate",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 39. Select correct word:",
        question: "Although the rest of the family had strong opinions about the matter, Maud felt quite _____.",
        options: ["Calm", "Indifferent", "Hysterical", "Relieved"],
        answer: "Indifferent",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 40. Select correct phrase:",
        question:
            "To combat climate change, industries are being urged to _____ emissions to help reduce the impact of global warming.",
        options: ["Cut back on", "Tackle", "Dump", "Break down"],
        answer: "Cut back on",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 41. Read and select the best option:",
        question:
            "John went to the store to buy apples. He wanted to make an apple pie for his family. The store did not have any apples left. John was disappointed.\n\nWhy did John go to the store?",
        options: ["To buy oranges.", "To buy apples.", "To make an apple pie.", "Because he was disappointed."],
        answer: "To make an apple pie.",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 42. Read and select the best option:",
        question:
            "When Martin first moved to New York, he found the city overwhelming. However, as months passed by, he adapted to the city’s fast pace and now enjoys the diverse culture and opportunities it offers.\n\nHow did Martin’s perception of New York change over time?",
        options: [
            "He found it overwhelming initially and now finds it boring.",
            "He first found it overwhelming, but now enjoys the city.",
            "He did not like the diverse culture initially.",
            "He still finds the city overwhelming.",
        ],
        answer: "He first found it overwhelming, but now enjoys the city.",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 43. Read and select the best option:",
        question:
            "While numerous studies underscore the relationship between education and societal development, we must be cautious not to mistake correlation for causation. The evolution of society is the result of a complex interplay of numerous factors, of which education is undoubtedly an integral part, but not the only driving force.\n\nAccording to the text, what is the role of education in societal development?",
        options: [
            "Education is the sole driving force of societal development.",
            "Education has no role in societal development.",
            "Education is an integral part, but not the only factor driving societal development.",
            "The role of education in societal development is entirely misunderstood.",
        ],
        answer: "Education is an integral part, but not the only factor driving societal development.",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Questions 44-49. Read the text:",
        question:
            "Tips that can help\n\nSix out of ten CV’s which are prepared by Information Technology professionals fail to meet the basic standards and are turned down without even being read fully, according to a recruitment company. As a consequence, thousands of candidates are excluding themselves from attractive job opportunities. Although the company handles over 60,000 CV’s per year, it estimates that at least 60% would not be admitted if they were sent directly to potential clients due to basic errors.\n\nThe company Marketing Director said, “Sadly it’s often the most highly qualified candidates whose CV’s are so poorly constructed that they are literally dead on arrival. Attractive job opportunities in the IT industry often generate intense competition and there is often little to choose between the candidates”.\n\n“Advice on the presentation format of CV’s in relation to the requirements that they are being submitted for should be an Industry standard so as to add real value to the candidates that you are representing and indeed to fulfil your professional obligations to your clients”.\n\n“Writing a CV can be extremely difficult and too often a CV turns out to be a generic overview including a lot of information that is irrelevant. People should remember that an employer typically spends between 15 and 30 seconds scanning each CV and you have that one chance to make an impression”.\n\n“A good CV is more than just documentation of your career path; it is a marketing tool designed to present your professional career experience according to the new job specification. It should also include details of past professional successes that effectively demonstrate your ability to undertake the job responsibilities outlined”.\n\nRecruitment companies say that potential clients ...",
        options: [],
        answer: "",
        points: 0,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 44. Read and select the best option from previous text:",
        question: "The Marketing Director said that the best candidates ...",
        options: ["Are the most affected", "Do not send CV`s", "Write the best CV`s"],
        answer: "Write the best CV`s",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 45. Read and select the best option from previous text:",
        question: "The Marketing Director suggests that candidates ought to pay attention to ...",
        options: ["CV`s presentation", "Other companies", "Other competitors"],
        answer: "CV`s presentation",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 46. Read and select the best option from previous text:",
        question: "The Marketing Director says that very often CV’s include ...",
        options: ["Necessary details", "Unimportant information", "Very little information"],
        answer: "Unimportant information",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 47. Read and select the best option from previous text:",
        question: "Candidates should remember that employers ...",
        options: ["Are typical people", "Are very busy people", "Make an impression on people"],
        answer: "Are very busy people",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
    {
        description: "Question 48. Read and select the best option from previous text:",
        question: "A good curriculum should represent ...",
        options: ["The new job specification", "Your marketing tools", "Your overall skills"],
        answer: "The new job specification",
        points: Math.floor(Math.random() * 5) + 1,
    },
];
